<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[PostMarshall blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://postmarshall.github.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://postmarshall.github.com/"/>
  <updated>2012-11-14T13:26:50+01:00</updated>
  <id>http://postmarshall.github.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Jelle Helsen]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Handling email as a team]]></title>
    <link href="http://postmarshall.github.com/blog/2012/11/08/handling-email-as-a-team/"/>
    <updated>2012-11-08T00:10:00+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://postmarshall.github.com/blog/2012/11/08/handling-email-as-a-team</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>If your team is relying on email to communicate with customers you have probably noticed email is a crappy tool to commucate as a team. You&#8217;re probable familiar with the following scenario:
   * A customer sends a mail to your team with a question.
   * Nick (one of your team members) replies to your customers email. Unless Nick is an email ninja he will be using his own email address. Nick&#8217;s reply will be stored in Nick&#8217;s Sent items folder.
   * The next day that same customers replies to Nick&#8217;s message. This message will go to Nicks inbox. Too bad Nick has his day off. Now you&#8217;re customer&#8217;s email won&#8217;t be answered till after the weekend.</p>

<p>Scenario&#8217;s like this are caused by a lack of good tools to handle that flood of email your team has to handle daily. This is because most email systems are designed with individuals in mind, not teams.</p>

<ul>
<li> Usually email is delivered to someone&#8217;s personal inbox instead of your team&#8217;s central mailbox</li>
<li> Some systems already have Public folders, which can be used as a team&#8217;s mailbox, but:

<ul>
<li>When you reply to a mail in a Public folder the from and reply-to address on your reply email will contain your personal address instead of the team&#8217;s address. This will move the conversation to your personal inbox, where your team cannot help you.</li>
<li>Your reply is stored in your Sent Items, where nobody of your team can reach it. This way none of your team members are aware of your reply.</li>
<li>You need IT staff to manage your mailboxes</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>


<p>These kind of scenarios could be avoided with the right tools. Enter PostMarshall:</p>

<ul>
<li> PostMarshall has true team mailboxes:

<ul>
<li>Email delivered to a team&#8217;s mailbox.</li>
<li>Replies to these mails will be stored in the team&#8217;s mailbox. This way the complete conversation can be viewed by the team.</li>
<li>Replies will get the team&#8217;s email address as a reply-to address. This way the conversation stays in your team&#8217;s mailbox giving your team a complete overview of the conversation.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li> No IT staff required.</li>
<li> Budget friendly solutions (no upfront investments required).</li>
</ul>


<p>Interested? <a href="http://www.postmarshall.com">Sign up</a> today.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
