<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[PostMarshall blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://postmarshall.github.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://postmarshall.github.com/"/>
  <updated>2012-11-26T00:02:05+01:00</updated>
  <id>http://postmarshall.github.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Jelle Helsen]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Google Apps mail groups don't work]]></title>
    <link href="http://postmarshall.github.com/blog/2012/11/25/why-google-apps-mail-groups-dont-work/"/>
    <updated>2012-11-25T22:26:00+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://postmarshall.github.com/blog/2012/11/25/why-google-apps-mail-groups-dont-work</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I found a good tutorial today on how to use group on a Google Apps account. You can find it <a href="http://nathalielussier.com/blog/technology-blog/google-apps-email-tutorial-for-team-members-or-virtual-assistants">here</a>. This tutorial boils down to the following:</p>

<ol>
<li>Create a group and give it an email address</li>
<li>Select the people that are part of the group</li>
<li>Set custom privileges on the group so it can receive mail from outside your organization</li>
<li>login to your email account</li>
<li>add a from address to your account</li>
<li>confirm that from address</li>
<li>setup the “Reply from the same address the message was sent to” option in your account</li>
<li>repeat step 4 to 7 for each member of the group</li>
</ol>


<p>This is way to complicated. If you need to create a group with 5 members this will take 23 steps! On top of that, how good this works, once you have it set up, depends mainly on the discipline of your team. With every mail you send you have to make sure you BCC the group to keep everyone in the loop. At one point someone will forget. There should be a simpler way to do this.</p>

<h4>Enter PostMarshall</h4>

<p>PostMarshall has real <em>shared</em> mailboxes. This means mails sent to your team don&#8217;t clutter up your personal inbox. Emails sent from the teams mailbox will be stored in the teams mailbox so all team members are kept in the loop. Creating a new shared mailbox is a matter of 4 simple steps:</p>

<ol>
<li>Click the &#8220;+&#8221; button</li>
<li>Enter the name of the mailbox</li>
<li>Select the people who should access the mailbox</li>
<li>Click &#8220;Create&#8221;</li>
</ol>


<p>This will create a shared mailbox and add it to each members mailbox list. There all team members can follow up on these mails. All replies are automatically sent from the correct email address. The replies itself will be stored next to the original mail so everyone can see the complete thread. No more clutter in your personal inbox. No more emails falling through the cracks.</p>

<p>PostMarshall is all about making life easier for teams using email. Interested? Sign up <a href="http://www.postmarshall.com">here</a>.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Handling email as a team]]></title>
    <link href="http://postmarshall.github.com/blog/2012/11/08/handling-email-as-a-team/"/>
    <updated>2012-11-08T00:10:00+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://postmarshall.github.com/blog/2012/11/08/handling-email-as-a-team</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>If your team is relying on email to communicate with customers you have probably noticed email is a crappy tool to commucate as a team. You&#8217;re probable familiar with the following scenario:</p>

<ul>
<li> A customer sends a mail to your team with a question.</li>
<li> Nick (one of your team members) replies to your customers email. Unless Nick is an email ninja he will be using his own email address. Nick&#8217;s reply will be stored in Nick&#8217;s Sent items folder.</li>
<li> The next day that same customers replies to Nick&#8217;s message. This message will go to Nicks inbox. Too bad Nick has his day off. Now you&#8217;re customer&#8217;s email won&#8217;t be answered till after the weekend.</li>
</ul>


<p>Scenario&#8217;s like this are caused by a lack of good tools to handle that flood of email your team has to handle daily. This is because most email systems are designed with individuals in mind, not teams.</p>

<ul>
<li> Usually email is delivered to someone&#8217;s personal inbox instead of your team&#8217;s central mailbox</li>
<li> Some systems already have Public folders, which can be used as a team&#8217;s mailbox, but:

<ul>
<li>When you reply to a mail in a Public folder the from and reply-to address on your reply email will contain your personal address instead of the team&#8217;s address. This will move the conversation to your personal inbox, where your team cannot help you.</li>
<li>Your reply is stored in your Sent Items, where nobody of your team can reach it. This way none of your team members are aware of your reply.</li>
<li>You need IT staff to manage your mailboxes</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>


<p>These kind of scenarios could be avoided with the right tools. Enter PostMarshall:</p>

<ul>
<li> PostMarshall has true team mailboxes:

<ul>
<li>Email delivered to a team&#8217;s mailbox.</li>
<li>Replies to these mails will be stored in the team&#8217;s mailbox. This way the complete conversation can be viewed by the team.</li>
<li>Replies will get the team&#8217;s email address as a reply-to address. This way the conversation stays in your team&#8217;s mailbox giving your team a complete overview of the conversation.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li> No IT staff required.</li>
<li> Budget friendly solutions (no upfront investments required).</li>
</ul>


<p>Interested? <a href="http://www.postmarshall.com">Sign up</a> today.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
